pokerheaven.com 2015-09-05

# Politica de confidentialitate | Poker Heaven | PokerHeaven.com

At Poker Heaven, we are committed to protecting the privacy of our customers. Our Privacy Policy shows how Poker Heaven uses and safeguards your personal information. We are committed to ensuring that we follow all relevant data protection legislation and we have a legal duty to protect any information we collect from you.

We commit not to share, sell, lease or lend your personal data or details regarding your winnings / losses with any third party unless it is necessary to do so for processing fund transactions and / or such information disclosure is required by law. The data is kept strictly confidential and the information is stored in a secure environment.

##  Marketing Preferences

When you register, please indicate whether you would like to receive information on products and services from us or other companies in our group by crossing in the appropriate box.

You may opt-out of receiving marketing communications at any time by following the instructions contained in each marketing message or by sending us an email at support@heavenbet.com.

##    
Player Data

We use a third party provider for payment processing. Although we no Take Responsibility for the Privacy policy of this Company, we CAN Ensure That Our customers we always reliable and professional Choose Partners.   
We May Also share customers' personal information with Our Affiliate Partners, But only if the Customer signed up to Poker Heaven That through partner and has approved Thereby Sharing such information.   
When you use Our ​​Poker Client Services, send us emails or contact us over Live Chat we collect and save the following personal information:

· First name and surname

· Date of birth

· Sex

· Full address

· Phone / mobile number

· Payment details

· IP address

· E-mail address

· Cookies

· Email history

##  Personal Information

Most of the personal information is supplied by the customer on a voluntary basis. Some information is gathered automatically by Poker Heaven, such as statistical data on the customer's use of our website. These statistics are used to improve the website.  

Poker Heaven will use your personal information for the following purposes:

· Verifying your identity and age. To use Poker Heavens services you need to be at least 18 years of age or at least the minimum permitted age in your legal jurisdiction if the minimum age restriction in your jurisdiction is greater than 18 years.

· IP address tracking against your user identification in order to prevent fraudulent activities.

· Email correspondence.

· Answering customer service queries.

· Customer profiling.

· Recording transactions on your account.

· Managing your account.

· Administering all fund transactions (processed by third party).

· Improvement information

· Including surveys.

· Statistical analysis and market research.

· Communicating promotions, special offers or other targeted communications by email or phone.

##  Customer interaction

As a customer we will send you e-mails or contact you by phone informing you of special promotions or other information relating to our poker services. If you wish to unsubscribe from emails you can either change your account settings in the poker client under "profile" or click "unsubscribe" in the bottom of any newsletter email sent to you.

Our Privacy Policy should be read together with our terms and conditions. When you click "I agree" you have given your consent to the processing of your personal data in accordance with the terms in our Privacy Policy. We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy and encourage you to periodically review it. If we change our privacy policy we will post the changes on this page. Your continued use of our services constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any updates.

##  Disclosures

We will only disclose personal information to other companies within our group of companies, business partners, government bodies and law enforcement agencies, future owners of our business and suppliers we engage to process data on our behalf only on a need to know basis. Disclosure to the relevant Authorities shall only be made in circumstance where we are legally required to do so.

##  Contact details

If you have Any Questions in regards to how we store your details, Please do not Hesitate to contact us at [support@pokerheaven.com](mailto:support@pokerheaven.com) . In accordance with applicable Malta and UK Data Protection laws we reserve the right to charge a fee for providing such information.
